Maribel Ellison 760-668-2316 maribel.duron86@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/maribel-ellison

Skills and Achievements

Experience with Mac OS X, Windows OS, Linux, Microsoft Office, iOS, web development using HTML, CSS, Git, and Java Code, fluent in Spanish. Previously certified, and willing to recertify, in the Salesforce.com Administration Certification (201), ServiceMax Administration Certification (101), and ServiceMax Advanced Administrator Certification (201). Inducted into Sunquest's Director's Circle of Excellence for keeping customer support statistics in the top 15% of the department, and awarded ServiceMax Inc's Top 40 award, which is presented to the top 40 employees in the company for outstanding performance.

Work Experience

Zinier Inc., April 2020 - November 2020 Technical Support Lead, LATAM (T3)

- Track tickets in Zendesk that are submitted by clients
- Designated mobile Subject Matter Expert (SME) for the Zinier mobile application
- Work with clients to verify functionality or issues with specified products
- Read JSON modules and workflows during troubleshooting
- Debug client issues using web developer console, Zinier platform logs, AWS logs via DataDog, API logs, and mobile logs (if applicable)
- Conduct screen shares to walk clients through resolutions or to better understand the issue
- Work with the engineers to resolve defects found product code by replicating issues and pinpointing the layer in which the issue is located
- Work with the Customer Support Managers (CSMs) to track, update, and push existing tickets towards resolution
- Worked on call hours to troubleshoot system down issues to resolution
- Assisted with/owned LATAM tickets as the only LATAM support agent for 8 months
- Ran scripts using PostMan to assist with client issues
- Assisted engineering with translating code into Spanish
- Created, updated, monitored tickets created through Jira to track enhancement requests, bugs, tasks, and internal feature requests
- Worked in Confluence to create, update, and approve Knowledge documents as well as search for information to assist with troubleshooting and training.

ServiceMax Inc., April 2019 - April 2020 Senior Support Manager

- Manage the Americas Critical Customer Support team (T3)
- Report on and record technician metrics to ensure that technicians exceed standards
- Host weekly one-on-one meetings in order to review metrics with technicians and provide mentoring where needed
- Assist in client and account manager escalations
- Consult with the client on the best practice for customizations and implementations.
- Head customization projects and ensure that the correct architect is matched with the work that is needed to be built out
- Debug client issues using Salesforce's debug logs, developer console, and mobile logs (if applicable)
- Create cases and work with salesforce.com technical support in order to provide timely resolutions to clients

- Travel to client locations to assist the account team in account retention by addressing any and all client open cases and any additional issues
- Assist in article creation for the ServiceMax Support Handbook

ServiceMax Inc., March 2018 - April 2019 Regional Support Manager

- Manage a team of five US West Technical Support Engineers
- Report on and record technician metrics to ensure that technicians exceed standards
- Host weekly one-on-one meetings in order to review metrics with technicians and provide mentoring where needed if they are not meeting the company's standards
- Assist in client and account manager escalations
- Assist in challenging cases and client hypercare during and after major releases to ensure that the client has no to little downtime
- Onboard and train new technical support engineers
- Provide coverage during alternating shifts or when regional managers are out of the office.
- Assist in training Team Leads/Regional Managers

ServiceMax Inc., February 2017 - March 2018 Customer Support Team Lead

- Track tickets in Salesforce.com that are submitted by customers
- Debug client issues using Salesforce's debug logs, developer console, and mobile logs (if applicable)
- Manage a team of five US West Technical Support Engineers
- Report on and record technician metrics to ensure that technicians exceed standards
- Host weekly one-on-one meetings in order to review metrics with technicians and provide mentoring where needed if they are not meeting the company's standards
- Conduct interviews for prospective candidates
- Onboard and train new technical support engineers
- Create a channel of communication between the Customer Account Managers and the Regional Team Leads in order to provide the best customer support experience

ServiceMax Inc., April 20, 2015 - February 2017 Technical Support Engineer

- Track tickets in Salesforce.com that are submitted by customers
- Work with clients to verify functionality or issues with specified products
- Debug client issues using Salesforce's debug logs, developer console, and mobile logs (if applicable)
- Assist in HTML doc changes for client output documents
- Conduct screen shares to walk clients through resolutions or to better understand the issue
- Work with the engineers to resolve defects found product code
- Create product solutions within salesforce.com and ServiceMax managed package to assist other agents and clients with troubleshooting steps for specific issues
- Create test environments to replicate client issues or test solutions

Sunquest Information Systems, Sept. 9, 2013 – April 17, 2015 Technical/Customer Service Support Specialist

- Track tickets in Salesforce.com that are submitted by customers
- Daily exposure to Mumps programming code for the Clinical Financial and Commercial Laboratory Sunquest company products
- Meet the 90 minute service level agreement
- Work with clients to verify functionality or issues with specified products
- Work with the engineers to resolve bugs found in the Mumps product code

- Create product solutions within Salesforce.com to assist other agents and clients with troubleshooting steps for specific issues
- Conducted client educational presentations in June 2014 during the company's annual convention
- Attended Salesforce.com's DreamForce 2014 event to assist with gathering information for future Salesforce implementations within the company
- Assisted in implementing the Salesforce console for use by all Support Specialists.
- Created a Salesforce Customer Community template for Sunguest clients
- Assisted with the Salesforce Knowledge implementation

Stream Global Services (Salesforce.com CRM Contract), Jan. 23, 2012 – May 23, 2013 Technical/Customer Service Support Professional

- Track tickets in Salesforce.com that are submitted by customers
- Daily exposure to Windows XP, Vista, 7, Mac OS X, iPhone, Android, Blackberry, and tablets.
- Meet two hour service level agreement call back requirements
- Experience with handling large call and case volumes
- Assisted with the Summer '12 and Winter '13 releases
- Performed password resets, created workflow rules, email alerts, email templates, consoles, objects, fields, users, hierarchies, reports, Salesforce for Outlook configurations, and mobile configurations.
- Log calls with pertinent information to allow customer to refer to notes in the future or as necessary
- Assist other agents by calling their customers
- Held 201 (211) Administrator certification, 301 Advanced Administrator certification, and 401 Developer Certification
- Work over time to assist with large work loads
- Coach and mentor new employees
- Use screen shares to assist customers with a resolution to the technical issues
- One of two bilingual technical support agents at my location

Labor Finders-Newnan, March 2010 – June 2010 & May 2011 – Oct. 2011 Office Manager and Assistant Branch Manager

- Accounts payable/receivable experience
- Microsoft Office Suite 2010 daily experience
- Filed and input data into StaffCom CRM to maintain current applicant files and tax information
- Maintained payroll for 300+ employees
- Experienced in answering multiline phones
- Assisted the collections department to keep our customers up to date on their payments
- Outside sales experience
- Submitted bill rate quotes to customers, set them up in the system
- Submitted workman's compensation forms to our corporate offices
- Submitted and conducted background checks and drug screens
- Gave new hire orientations and conducted interviews
- Filled out and submitted unemployment paperwork in a timely manner

Clayton County Sheriff's Office -Jonesboro, GA June 2010-May 2011 Court Security Officer

- Shackle and hand-cuff inmates
- Place inmates into the correct cells for court
- Escort inmates to court
- Maintain the safety of inmates and co-workers

U.S. Army, June 24, 2004-Jan. 29, 2010 Wheel Mechanic, Public Affairs Journalist, Black Hawk Mechanic

- Public Affairs Journalist at Fort Irwin
- Typed 5 to 7, 500 word articles per week
- Daily use of Microsoft Outlook, Excel, Spreadsheet and Word
- Archived old newspapers, edited rough drafts, answered multi-line phones, maintained my supervisor's calendar and directed customers accordingly
- Deployed 14 months in Iraq
- I PCS'd to Fort Riley, Kansas where I was honorably discharged after 4 months.

Education

- Currently attending University of Arizona Coding Boot Camp with a tentative completion of 12 July
- Graduate of Colorado Technical University Online in June 2015 with a Bachelor's in Science of Information Technology with a concentration in Security
- Graduate of Keiser University in July 2011 with an Associate in the Science of Medical Assisting
- Graduate of North Medford High School in 2004 from Medford, Oregon

References available upon request.